[Music]
right now
we're facing a man-made disaster
of global scale
our greatest threat in thousands of
years
climate change
if we don't take action
the collapse of our civilizations
and the extinction
of much of the natural world
is on the horizon
[Music]
the world's people have spoken
their message is clear
time is running out
the amount of carbon dioxide in the
atmosphere now is 50 higher than it was
in 1900
and not only are we piling in more and
more carbon dioxide in the atmosphere
but we are chopping down the forests of
the earth at a great rate
and the forests themselves are the most
efficient consumers of carbon dioxide
that there are on earth
we're going to destroy the ground
because the soil of a rainforest isn't
very good we are actually tampering with
the climate of the earth and with the
very atmosphere that we breathe
when we talk about the disappearance of
the ozone layer
we don't know what will happen when the
ozone layer goes
the world has become so fragile
that we cannot subject the earth
to the tortures we can now inflict upon
it
when we talk about the greenhouse effect
we're talking about something
that affects the entire earth
and these problems are life and death
problems
they go to the root of the viability of
the planet itself
[Music]
so there's one thing that is
biologically certain
about the human species is that it is a
human species
one species
if we don't stop the destruction of our
natural world nothing else will matter
simply put if we don't protect nature
we can't protect ourselves
[Music]
the only way we can solve a problem
is by a human solution
never can we sit back and wait for
miracles to save us
miracles don't happen
sweat happens
efforts happens
thought happens
[Music]
you